Mikaila K Ivery

Business Number: $+1929-479-1579 \cdot Email: iverymikaila@gmail.com \cdot Website: mikailaivery.com Brooklyn, New York, 11236$

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Front-End Developer with proven experience at Boy Blondey, Orée Nyc, and Brooklyn House of Hair in helping companies create and maintain a better code base for reusability. Capable of bridging any knowledge gaps through continuous learning from senior developers while still coaching novice developers. Experience in facilitating projects from concept to launch. Passionate about learning and growth with a desire to apply skills on a larger development team.

KEY COMPETENCIES

HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript Responsive Design Mobile-First Websites React.js | React Native State Management | Redux Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Bootstrap | Performance Testing Adobe Creative Suite

Feb 2023 - Jul 2023

Object-Oriented Programming

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Boy Blondey Feb 2022 - Present

Freelance Web Developer

Developed user interfaces with modern Javascript framework React.js, HTML5, and CSS3, which improved user satisfaction. Created accessible, responsive, and functional code that allowed web visitors on any device to have the same user experience. Designed and coded custom HTML email templates that work with any email provider.

Orée Nyc Sep 2022 - Present

Freelance Web Developer

Designed high-fidelity prototypes in Figma that accurately reflected client needs and preferences. Designed and coded mock designs and wireframes for landing pages for highly anticipated product drops. Worked as part of a 4 person team and communicated in a professional and collegial way.

Brooklyn House of Hair

Freelance Web Developer

Developed and designed custom HTML, CSS, and Javascript for the brand's Shopify website, resulting in improved website functionality and customer satisfaction. Maintained quality website functionality through ongoing updates and troubleshooting.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Associate of Applied Science

Major: Advertising Marketing Communications Fashion Institute of Technology 2019 - 2021

Web Development Certification

SheCodes Workshops 2021-2022

HTML Email Bootcamp

Noble Desktop 2022

SCHOOL PROJECTS

Weather App

Technologies: Open Weather Map API, React.js Source Code: <u>GitHub</u>

Dictionary App

Technologies: Dictionary API, React.js

Source Code: GitHub